SABOJISE

WEB DEVELOPER

EXPERIENCE

Music & Worship Director | Maple Ridge Community Church

JAN 2019 - DEC 2019, MAPLE RIDGE, BC

- Accountable for direct Worship Team support, with a track of building sustainable relationships.
- Spearheaded development and execution of worship initiatives on behalf of church elders generating excellence and consistency to Sunday services of 400 congregation.

Music Instructor & Coordinator | Youth With A Mission

JAN 2006 - DEC 2018, PERTH, AUSTRALIA

- Managed and mentored a multi-cultural team of musicians over a period of 6-9 years in development of skills, resource management, networking, music production and marketing.
- Designed and developed a six-month music curriculum with focus on ethnomusicology, training an average of 15 – 20 musicians each year.

EDUCATION

BrainStation | Diploma, Web Development

MAY 2020 - SEPT 2020, VANCOUVER, BC

Shaw Academy | Diploma, Mobile App Development

SEPT 2017 - JAN 2018, DUBLIN CO, DUBLIN (online)

PROJECTS

Click **HERE** to view projects or https://sabojise.herokuapp.com

sajiyoonline@gmail.com 778-512-8464 linkedin.com/in/sabojise/ github.com/Sabzs

SKILLS

Front-End: HTML, CSS, SASS,

JavaScript, React.js, Document Object

Model (DOM) APIs

Back-End: Node.js, Express.js, Web

APIs, User Authentication

Databases: MySQL, **ORMs:** Sequelize

Deployment & Deployment Tools:

Heroku, GitHub, WebPack

PROFILE

Blending a background of 15 years as a musician with a strong skill set honed through several years of writing, producing and managing bands. I bring a music perspective and band managing approach to web development.

Persistence, self-discipline and attention to detail are my key strengths. My strengths help me to resolve ambiguity and raise the bar on the thoroughness of web development. I look forward to exercising my passion for combining technology and the desire to create unique solutions that people can feel, interact and work with.